《迷失》前情提要...
Previously on "lost"
说吧
Now talk.
这个岛
Think of the island
就像留声机上的唱片
Like a record spinning on a turntable,
只不过  现在唱片一直在跳格
Only now, that record is skipping.
不管Linus在兰花站下做了什么
Whatever ben linus did down at the orchid station,
可能把我们驱逐了
It may have... dislodged us.
从哪驱逐出去
Dislodged us from what?
时间
Time.
不是吧
Come on! aah!
根本不会停了
It's not stopping!
Charlotte
Charlotte!
我们要回兰花站
We have to go back to the orchid.
一切从那里开始
That's where all this started.
或许能在那里结束
maybe it's where it'll stop.
会发生这一切  只因他们离开了
This is all happening because they left.
如果能把他们带回来  应该能停止
I think it'll stop if i can bring them back.
带谁回来
Bring who back?
Jack  Sun  Sayid  Hugo  Kate
Jack, sun, sayid, hugo, kate.
你难道不想让她回来吗
don't you want her to come back?
你确定不要我们拉你下去
You sure you don't want us to lower you down?
那就没意思了
Where would be the fun in that?
John  妈的  抓紧
John! damn it, hold on!
可以放手了
I think you can let go of that now.
不
No.
不  不  不
No! no! no! no! no!
James  别这样
James, don't.
快点  帮我
Come on! help me!
James
James...
别挖了
Stop.
我们帮不了他
We can't help him.
不管John去了哪  他已经不见了
Wherever john went, he's gone.
不管我们在哪  那口井还没建呢
And wherever we are is before that well was ever built.
而且相当久远
Yeah, i'd say way before.
你怎么
What makes you--
James
James!
能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?!
有人吗
Can anyone hear me?!
究竟怎么回事
What the hell was that?
这次不一样
That one was different. it was...
简直跟地震一样
That was more like an earthquake.
-Locke  -James  等等
Locke! james, wait!
真好
Great.
我的头不疼了
My headache is gone.
我的也是
Yeah, mine is, too.
鼻子也不留血了
And my nose isn't bleeding anymore.
看来结束了
I think it's over.
看来John成功了
I think john did it.
现在怎么办
Now what?
我们等他回来
Now we wait for him to come back.
等多久
For how long?
要多久等多久
As long as it takes.
三年后
Three Years Later
有没有搞错
Are you kidding me?
我才离开10分钟  你们就跳起舞来了
I'm gone ten minutes, and you're having a
别这么扫兴嘛
hootenanny? Don't be such a bummer,man.
Rosie才刚刚进入状态
Rosie was just droppin' off some brownies.
你应该谢谢她
You should thank her. yeah.
她不该来这里  Jerry  我们在值班呢
She shouldn't be here, jerry. we're on the clock, man.
放松点  Phil  能出什么事啊
Ah, mellow out, phil. w-what's gonna happen, huh?
北极熊又不会从笼子里跑出来
The polar bears are gonna figure a way out
这个不是重点
of their cages? That's not the point.
要是被Lafleur知道了
If lafleur finds outwhat you're doing
Lafleur不会知道的
lafleur's not gonna find out anything.
吃亏的人是我
It's gonna be my ass, man.
-我才是要向他汇报的人  -伙计们
I'm the one who's gonna have to answer to him. guys?
-放松  没有人会知道  -伙计们
Relax, man. nobody's gonna find out. guys. what...
不
No.
是敌人吗
Is that a hostile?
不知道
I don't know.
那是
Is that...
Horace吗
Horace?
他手里有炸药
Oh, he's got dynamite. aah!
带她出去  快带她出去
Get her out of here! get her out of here now! now!
快走,Rosie 你得出去了,别跟任何人说你来过
Come on, rosie. You gotta get outta here now.Don't tell anyone you were here.
我跟你说了别带她来
I told you not to bring her here. i told you!
快走  糟了
Just go. go! okay, this is bad.
糟了  完蛋了  我们要通知Lafleur
this is bad, man. This is bad, man. We gotta get lafleur.
早上3点  你真的想
3:00 in the morning. do you really wanna
-吵醒他  -当然不想
wake laflr up? No, of course not, but--
或者我们自己解决
No, no, no. maybe--maybe we can handle this ourselves,
要是Horace把自己炸了
And maybe Horace blows himself up,
Lafleur就会怪我们没叫醒他  快走
And lafleur kills us for not waking him. we gotta go now!
你去敲门
Do you wanna knock?
你去敲
You knock.
好吧
Fine.
干嘛
What?
Lafleur先生  抱歉打扰您
Mr. lafleur, sorry to bother you,
但防御系统那边出了点情况
But we got a situation out at the pylons.
什么情况
What kind of situation?
是Horace
Uh, it's, uh, horace.
他拿了炸药  在炸树
He's got dynamite, and he's blowing up trees.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：蚊子   zerk   lsaac_W   娜姬雅   rosemaryai
时间轴：雨中泪    校对：蚊子   lsaac_W   娜姬雅
■
后期：冰河     总监：非燕
行了  我来了
Relax! i'm comin'!
老大
Hey, boss.
晚上好  Enos  带了遥控器吗
Evening, enos. you got your zapper with ya?
带了  为什么要带这个
Yep. you wanna tell me why i need it?
因为大胆的头领在炸树呢
'cause our fearless leader is out blowing up trees.
他干嘛这么做
Why's he doing that?
因为带了炸药呗
'cause he's loaded.
Horace什么时候开始喝酒了
Since when does horace drink?
没喝  所以要保持低调别让人知道
He doesn't, so we're gonna keep this on the down low.
天啊
Oh, man.
好了  把火灭了  收好炸药
All right. you put out that fire. pack up this dynamite.
我带他回去
I'll take him home.
干嘛你不去灭火收炸药
Why don't you put out the fire, pack up,
我带他回去
And--and i'll take him home? you
你想去跟Amy说在哪找到他的吗
wanna tell amy where we found him?
帮我拉他起来
Help me get him up.
天啊  他没事吧
Oh, my god. is he okay?
-你说呢  -带他进来吧
You tell me. bring him inside.
放沙发就行
The couch. the couch is fine.
在哪找到他的
Oh. where'd you find him?
火堆边  在炸树呢
By the flame, blowing up trees with dynamite.
能说说为什么吗
Wanna tell me why?
我们吵架了
We had a fight.
一定吵得挺凶
Must've been a doozy.
拜托  Jim
Please, jim.
这是私事
It's personal.
隐私对吧  你认为人家不会知道
Personal? you think this isn't gonna get out?
等到早餐时,就人尽皆知了
It'll be on the coconut telegraph by breakfast.
是关于Paul
It was about Paul.
说下去
Go on.
怎么了  还好吗
What's the matter? you okay?
我要生了
The baby--it's coming.
天呐
Oh, hell.
三年前
Three Years Earlier
我不会告诉她的
I'm not gonna tell her.
不要告诉她  我不会...
Don't even tell her. i won't.
-红发美女去哪儿了  -不知道
-Where's Red?  -i don't know.
不  我不会告诉她  不会告诉她
No. i won't do it. i won't tell her.
-不会的   -Daniel
-I won't do it. won't...  -daniel?
你怎么了
You okay?
我不会那样么做的  我不会告诉她的
I'm not gonna do it. i'm not gonna tell her.
Daniel  Charlotte在哪儿
Daniel, where's charlotte?
她不在了
She's not here.
她...
She...
她不见了
She's gone.
去哪里了
Where?
她...死了
She's... dead.
她死了
She's dead.
刚又闪了一次亮光  然后
There was another flash, and...
她就不见了
And she was... she was just gone.
她的尸体就
Her... body just...
消失了
Disappeared.
她被亮光闪走了  我们留下了
She moved on, and we stayed.
我很难过
I'm so sorry.
等等  你说我们"留下了"
Hold on. wait a minute. we "stayed"?
我们不会再穿梭时间了吗
We're not traveling through time
结束了吗
anymore? you say it's over?
当然结束了
Of course it's over.
不管我们现在在哪
Wherever we are now...
不管现在是哪个时间
Whenever we are now...
我们永远留下了
We're here for good.
-我不会那样做的  -好了
-I won't do it. -okay. okay.
-我不会的  -好了
-I won't. i'm not gonna-- i'm--i'm... -okay.
太好了
Okay. swell.
等Dan回过神来 我们应该回海滩
Until dan checks back in, I say we head back to the beach.
等Locke带所有人回来时
When locke gets back with everybody,
-他们会在那里找我们  -海滩吗
-That's where they'll be looking for us. -the beach?
难道你还没挨够火箭啊
What, you didn't get enough flaming arrows shot at you?
你的帐篷都不在了  何必呢
And your camp is gone. why bother?
Sawyer说得对  Miles
Sawyer's right, Miles.
我们应该回海滩
We should go back to the beach.
我们可以再次生活在那里
We survived there before. we can do
-和以前一样  -说不定到了那里
-it again. -or maybe when we get there
你们又想回兰花站了
You'll--you'll wanna go back to the orchid again.
等在那里呆烦了
And then when that gets boring,
我们又可以回海滩
we can back to the beach.
你们只有这2个选择
It's the only two plans you people have.
收起你这套  我要去海滩了
Hey, zip it. i'm heading back to the beach.
帐篷在那好  不在我们就再建一个
If our stuff's there, great. if not, we build new stuff.
你不喜欢  就祝你好运
You don't like the plan, good luck.
他还领导上我们了
Who put him in charge?
谢谢你刚才为我说话
Thanks for getting my back for that whole beach issue.
你确实该谢我  这是个愚蠢的方案
You should thank me. it was a stupid idea.
那你干嘛要同意
Well, what does that say about you agreeing with me?
这样总比没计划好
Any plan is better than no plan.
另外  如果我不同意你
Besides, if i hadn't agreed with you,
我们现在还在争论下一步该怎样走
We'd still be arguing about where to go next.
我只是希望在我们到达海滩之前
I just hope you figure out something better
-你能想出更好的办法  -我虚心接受意见
-Before we get there. -well, i'm open to suggestions.
不  不  Paul  天呐
Oh, no! no, paul! oh, god! oh, god! no, no, no, no!
别  求你了  我们不知道
No, please! we didn't know!
Paul  求你了  阻止他
Paul, please, please do something. no, no.
别  别  我们只是来游玩的
No, no, no, no, no. we were just touring this park.
我们没别的意思  我们只是...Paul
We didn't mean anything. we were just having--paul.
Paul  求你了
Paul, please.
啊  天呐  别
Oh, my god! no!
别  Paul 求你了
No, paul, please. please.
你认为他们是谁
Who do you think they are?
无所谓  我们都不知道他们在什么时间
Who cares who they are? we don't even know when they are.
Dan
Dan.
我们不要介入  对吧  你之前是这么说的吧
We don't get involved, right? that's what you said.
我们做什么都无所谓了
Doesn't matter what we do.
该发生的终究会发生
Whatever happened, happened.
好  谢谢你  柏拉图
Yeah, thanks anyway, plato.
我要过去  你还会帮我吧
I'm going over there. you still got my back?
当然
Absolutely.
-Paul  醒醒啊  -跪下
-Paul, paul. talk to me! talk to me, paul! -on your feet!
-别  我不  -起来  快
-No, i can't! i can't! -come on, get up! now!
起来
up!
放下武器
All right, drop the gun!
天呐
Oh, god.
没事了
It's all right.
没事了  你安全了
It's okay. you're safe. it's over.
你是谁
Who are you?
她的朋友穿着达摩连衣裤
Her friend's wearing a dharma jumpsuit.
也就是70或80年代
That put us '70s, '80s.
-带着包的家伙  是其他人吗  -难倒我了
-The guys with the bags-- others? -beats me.
-你和他们不认识吗  -他们不在我的时代
-What, y'all don't know each other? -before my time.
Sawyer
Sawyer.
对讲机
Walkie.
我们得走了
We need to go.
马上来
I'm on it.
听着  我们要走了
Listen, sweetheart, we gotta get moving now.
你们是谁
Who are you people?
我们的船在去塔希提岛的航线上失事了
Our ship wrecked here on the way to tahiti.
但现在不重要了
But that ain't important right now,
因为对讲机另一边的人
'cause whoever's on the other end of this--
他们可能在我们救你前给那边的人通过话
Those two might've given 'em a call before we saved you.
我们得埋掉他们
We have to bury them.
埋掉吗  我们没时间
Bury them? we ain't got time to bury nobody.
我们必须埋  有停战协议
we--we--we have to. The truce.
天呐
Oh, god.
我们得埋掉他们
We have to bury them.
而且我们得
And--and we have...
我们得
We have...
把他带回家
And we have to bring it-- him back home.
我们得带上Paul
We have to bring paul back with us.
求你了
Please.
Please?
求你们了
Please.
我来扛他
I'll carry him.
好吧  我们埋掉他们
All right, we'll put these guys in the ground
带你的朋友回去  但必须抓紧时间
And carry your friend back, but we better do it fast.
他不是我的朋友
He wasn't... my friend.
他是我的丈夫
He was my husband.
好吧  听好了
All right, listen up.
我们到那之后  将会出现一连串问题
When we get there, there's gonna be a lot of questions.
到时你只需要把嘴闭上
So just keep your mouth shut.
我来跟他们谈
Let me do the talking.
你确定你能让他们相信
Do you really think you can convince them
我们沉船了吗
That we were in a boat wreck?
我是专家级的  欺骗是我赖以生存的技能
I'm a professional. I used to lie for a living.
Daniel  等等
Daniel! Stop!
把它关了
Turn it off.
-把什么关了  -不管是什么  反正给我关了
- Turn what off?  - Whatever that is.
可能是什么音波围墙之类的东西
It looks like some sort of sonic fence or something.
你刚说你们的船要去哪
Where did you say your ship was going?
听着 妹子  我们救了你的命 并且掩盖了那些尸体
Listen, sister, we're the ones who just saved your life And hid those bodies.
你还是相信我们  然后把那个东西关掉吧
So how about you trust us and turn that damn thing off?
好吧
Okay.
好  可以
Okay, fine.
音波围墙  我之前说过了由我来说话  记得吗
"Sonic fence"? Didn't I say let me do the talking?
再走一步  Dan的脑袋就烧焦了
One more step, Dan would've fri his brain.
他大脑早烧焦了
His brain has already been fried.
好了  关掉了
Okay, it's off.
你先走
You first.
看到吗  没问题的
See? it's fine.
好吧  我们走
All right, let's go.
我们继续走  大家做好自己的事情
And going forward, we should all do a better job.
三年后
Three Years Later
太疼了
It hurts!
你会好起来了的 Amy  放松一点
You're gonna be okay, Amy. Just try and relax.
Horace在哪
Where's Horace?
-他知道他的妻子临产吗  -他来不了
- Does he know his wife's in labor?  - He's unavailable.
听着  Amy的处境现在十分危险
Look, Amy's in a very dangerous situation.
-因为婴儿是臀位分娩  -什么意思
- The baby's breech.  - What the hell that means?
它是颠倒的  她需要剖腹产
It's upside down. She needs a caesarean.
别跟我说这么多  你就赶紧做吧
Well, don't tell me about it. Just do it.
我只是个内科医生  不是产科医生
I'm an internist, not an obstetrician.
我们的女性一般会在大陆进行接生
Our women always deliver on the mainland.
Amy本应在周二生产
Amy was supposed to get on the sub on tuesday.
婴儿比预期早到了两周
The baby's two weeks early.
-你到底能否为这个婴儿接生  -我不知道
- Can you deliver this baby or not?  - I don't know.
兄弟  她人呢
Hey, man. Where is she?
-怎么了  -Amy正在生孩子
- What's up?  -Amy's having her baby.
什么
What?
你听见没有
Did you hear me?
她遇到麻烦了
She's in trouble.
医生说她需要剖腹产
Doc says she needs a caesarean.
我们有协议的  别管你的协议了
We had an agreement. screw our agreement.
他从来没做过接生  我想你应该做过
He ain't never done one. i'm guessing you have.
你难道不明白吗
Don't you understand that every time
在岛上为女人接生
I try to help a woman on this island give birth,
是不会成功的
It hasn't worked?
这次没尝试过
Well, maybe whatever made that happen
你怎么就知道一定会失败
Hasn't happened yet.
你得试试  你得帮她
You gotta try. You gotta help her.
你是唯一一个能帮她的人
You're the only one that can.
婴儿的臀位分娩
The baby's breech.
-是的  -你试过外回转术吗
- Yes, but-- - Did you try an external cephalic version?
-什么  没有  -可能也太晚了
- What? No.  - I-- It's probably too late.
我需要一个12号手术刀以及14厚度的缝线
I'm gonna need a number 12 scalpel, 14-gauge sutures--
要半圆的  以及硬脑膜外麻醉剂
Half-round if you've got them-- and an epidural anesthetic.
你需要这些吗  Horace到底在哪
You're gonna need? where is horace?
我正在表达Horace的意见
I'm speaking for Horace now,
她正在为Amy接生这个婴儿
And I say she's delivering this baby.
我不认同这种做法
I don't think it's a good idea.
我要她帮我接生
I want her to do it
你听到了没有
You heard the lady.
听着  你一定要做好了
Listen... you're gonna do great.
我知道你可以的
I know you are.
好吧
Okay.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
Amy正在分娩
Amy went into labor.
我知道
I know.
她还好吧
Is she okay?
我不知道  出现了个问题
I don't know. There's a problem.
-Juliet在里面  -Juliet
- Juliet's in there.  - Juliet?
我让她过来帮忙了
I pulled her out of retirement.
有什么消息么
Any luck?
今天我们完成了1-3-3
We finished grid 1-3-3 today.
没发现我们的人
No sign of our people.
一个也没有
No one.
那再试试1-3-4吧
Well, 1-3-4 then.
我们还得持续多久  James
How long do we look, James?
继续下去吧
As long as it takes.
怎么了
What happened?
是个男孩
It's a boy.
母子平安吗
He's okay? She's okay?
都很好
Everyone's okay.
你头怎么样了
How's your head?
很疼
It hurts.
-我们的人呢  -他们很好
- Where are my people?  -They're fine.
Amy告诉我在丛林里发生的事情了
Amy told me what happened in the jungle,
我很感激你的所作所为
And I really appreciate what you did.
你的感激方式真的很特别
Well, y'all got a funny way of showing your appreciation.
我们有一些自卫的礼仪
We have certain defense protocols.
因为有许多不友善的土著人在这个岛上
There are hostile indigenous people on this island,
我们无法与他们正常相处
And we don't get along with them.
你还是告诉我你到底是谁吧
So... why don't you tell me who the hell you are?
我叫James Lafleur  你可以叫我Jim
My name's James Lafleur. you can call me Jim.
你怎么来到这个岛上的  Jim
How'd you get to the island, Jim?
如果我的朋友们没事  你干嘛问我这么多问题
If my friends are safe, why are you asking me all the questions.
他们告诉我要跟你谈
They told me I need to talk to you,
因为你是船长
That you're the boat captain.
我们遇到了一场暴风雨
We got caught in a storm.
我们的船沉了
Our ship wrecked.
我们撞到了暗礁上
Must've hit the reef.
谢天谢地  我们被冲到了海岸上
Thankfully, we washed up on shore.
是什么样的船
What kind of ship?
一个救助打捞船
A salvage vessel.
打捞知名沉船用的
Searching for a famous lost wreck.
是一艘贩运奴隶的船  来自英格兰的朴茨茅斯
It's an old slaver out of Portsmouth, England,
名叫  Black Rock
Called "the black rock."
你听说过么
You heard of her?
没听说过
Can't say that I have.
你被冲到了海岸上
So... once you got washed ashore,
那你为何又会在丛林里游荡
Why were you then wandering around in the jungle?
我们的一些船员失踪了  我们正在找他们
Some of our crew were missin'. We were looking for 'em.
后来我们就遇到了你的人  Amy
That's when we came upon your girl instead.
我告诉你吧  Jim
Well... I tell you what, Jim.
你们的人一出现  我们就会
If your crew shows up, we'll send
把你跟他们一起送到大溪地去
'em along with yaou off in Tahiti.
送到哪儿去
Send them where?
那里有搜潜艇 一大早就离岛
There's a submarine That leaves this island first thing in the morning.
你和你的朋友们  一定要上艇
You and your friends, you're gonna get on it.
潜艇会把你们送到大溪地
It's gonna drop you off in Tahiti.
从那儿你们就能回家了
You can find your way home from there.
等一下  Jim
Hold on a minute, Jim.
我们刚刚救了那女的一命
We just saved that woman's life.
能不能换一两个礼拜
Doesn't that earn us a week or two
-让我们找找其他人  -不行
- To find the rest of our people? - Nope.
只有授权居住在围场里的人
Only people that are allowed to stay on this compound
才是Dharma组织的成员
Are members of the Dharma Initiative.
而且  以防你误解
And look, i don't want you to take this the wrong way,
不好意思  Jim  你不够资格进Dharma
Please, jim, but you are not Dharma material.
咱们上当了
We're screwed.
他现在八成在使劲解释时空旅行
He's probably trying to explain time travel by now.
Sawyer不会有事的
Sawyer's gonna be fine.
你怎么看
What are you lookin' at?
我在这里住了3年多
I lived here for over three years.
那栋就是我的房子
That was my house over there.
你难道是Dharma组织的
You were in the Dharma Initiative?
不是
No.
后来  其他人夺取了这个兵营
The others took over these barracks
除掉了住在这里的绝大部分人
And wiped out most of the people living in them.
很久以后  我才被他们用潜艇带到岛上
They brought me here on a sub a long time after that.
那么...欢迎回家
Well... welcome home.
Daniel  还能想起来什么吗
Daniel... no more flash?
想不起来
No.
什么也想不起来
No more flash.
唱片又开始旋转
The record is spinning again.
我们不得不收听这首我们根本不想听的歌
We're just not on the song we wanna be on.
-爸爸呢  -过来  宝贝
- Where's dad? - Come on, love.
Charlotte
大家好
Hello.
稍后会有人陪同你们
Somebody will be along shortly
带大家去各自房间
To show you to your rooms.
同时 Lafleur 先生会跟你们介绍情况
In the meantime, Mr. Lafleur here can fill you in on the situation.
Lafleur先生?
"Mr. Lafleur"?
我瞎说的  现编的
It's creole. improvised.
你俩都说什么了
What happened in there?
他相信了我说的故事  但是他撒手不管咱们了
Well, he believed my story. But we're gettin' punted.
这混蛋明早要把咱们送上潜艇
The bastard's puttin' us on their sub tomorrow
-然后把咱们送到大溪地  -大家觉得这个坏消息怎么样
- And shipping us off to Tahiti. - How's that bad news?
大家快一点  快
You guys, come on! Now!
快走  进屋  进屋  快进屋
Let's go! get in! get in! move!
咱们走  离开这里  快点  快啊
Let's go! Get out of here! Come on! Come on!
快啊  进去  动起来  快
Come on! Inside! Move! Now!
Heather  看着他们
Heather, keep an eye on them.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
你好  Alpert先生
Hello, Mr. Alpert.
你好  Goodspeed先生
Hello, Mr. Goodspeed.
我更希望你来之前能事先通知我一下
I wish you would've told me you were coming.
那样的话  我可以帮你把栅栏撤了
I would've turned the fence off for you.
栅栏能隔开很多东西  但是隔不开我们
That fence may keep other things out, but not us.
Horace  唯一能隔开咱俩的
The only thing that does keep us out, Horace,
只有休战
Is our truce...
而你打破了休战协议
Which you've now broken.
我不明白你指的是什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我那两个人呢
Where are my two men?
你们绝不觉得
You know what?
上潜艇这事越听越像个好主意了
Gettin' on that sub is starting to sound like a great idea.
你们觉得怎么样  上潜艇  有人有意见吗
What do you say? Sub. Anyone?
管住你那张嘴  班仔
Hold your horses, banzai.
我看没人会上潜艇
I think no one's gonna on that sub.
Lafleur  你能把那些尸体埋了吗
Okay, Lafleur, how well do you bury those bodies?
得看看他们硬没硬
Well, that depends on how hard he looks.
给箭羽站打电话  通知他们进入一级战备
Call the Arrow. Tell them we're at condition one.
带上重武器 确保围栏电量最大
Take the heavy ordnance, and make sure the fence is at maximum.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
-让我跟他谈谈  -你说什么
- Let me talk to him. - Excuse me?
就是外面那个画眼线的 让我跟他谈谈
Your buddy out there with the eyeliner-- Let me talk to him.
我们跟这些人有停战协议 你不清楚状况
We had a truce with these people. You don't understand.
我清楚状况 是我杀了他两个弟兄
I understand I'm the one that killed his men,
我现在就要出去
And I'm the man that's gonna go out there
告诉他我为什么这样做
And tell him why I did it.
我可不是在跟你要许可
Well, it's a good thing I ain't asking your permission.
James  你确定自己在做什么吗
James, are you sure you know what you're doing?
不完全  但是我会弄清楚的
Not yet. But I'll figure somethin' out.
你好  Richard
Hello, Richard.
不好意思  咱们认识吗
I'm sorry. Do we know each other?
是我杀的你两个兄弟
I'm the guy that killed your men.
我当时听到枪声
Heard some gunshots,
看到两个男人向一位女士头上扔包
Saw two men throwing a bag over a woman's head.
我警告他们放下武器离开
Gave 'em a chance to throw the weapons down and walk away,
但是其中一人向我开枪  我就自我防卫了
But one of them took a shot at me, and i defended myself.
真是这样吗
Is that so?
真是这样
That's so.
你们的人知不知道你来跟我说这些
Your people know that you're telling me this?
他们不是我的人  所以如果你们之前有什么停战协议
They ain't my people, hoss. So if you got some kind
那就没被打破
Of a truce with them, it ain't been broken.
如果你不是Dharma组织的
If you're not a member of the Dharma Initiative,
那你是谁
Then what are you?
你把炸弹埋了吗
Did you bury the bomb?
就是那个上面写着大笨蛋的氢弹
The hydrogen bomb with "jughead" written on the side.
-你埋了吗  -你怎么...
- Did you bury it? - How...
我就是知道
Yeah, I know about it.
我还知道20年前
I also know that 20 years ago,
有个光头一瘸一拐走进你的营地
Some bald fella limped into your camp
胡言乱语  说要当你们的领袖
And fed you some mumbo jumbo about being your leader.
然后啪一下
And then poof...
他就在你眼前消失了
He went and disappeared right in front of ya.
想起来了吗
Any of this ringin' a bell?
那人叫John Locke
That man's name is John Locke,
我一直在等他回来
And I'm waitin' for him to come back.
那么
So...
你还觉不觉得我跟该死的Dharma组织是一伙的
You still think i'm a member of the damn Dharma Initiative?
不
No.
我绝对不这样想
I guess i don't.
但是无论你是谁
But no matter who you are,
我两个弟兄死了
Two of my men are dead.
我的人民需要个说法
And my people need some kind of justice.
我们现在该怎么办
Now what are we gonna do about that?
Amy  你怎么样了
How are you doing, Amy?
他走了吗
Is he gone?
我是说Alpert
Alpert?
不  他没走  我告诉他尸体的埋藏地点
No, he's not gone. We told him where the bodies were.
你告诉他了  为什么
You told him? why?
情势所迫
We had to.
只有这样  才能保住停火协议
It was the only way to maintain the truce.
Jim和他一起促成了停火  但是
Jim here worked it out with him, but...
他现在要从我们这里拿点东西
Well, he's gonna need something from us now.
他要把Paul的尸体一块儿带回去
He needs to take Paul's body back with him.
不
No.
Ames
Hey, Ames.
听着
Listen, w--
我们是老朋友了  对吗
We've been friends for a long time, yeah?
所以选择权完全在你
So this is completely your choice.
如果你不想把他给他们
If you don't want to give him to them,
我们就得承担后果
Then we will suffer the consequences.
让他们带走吧
They can take him.
他想维护我们的安全
He would want to keep us safe.
我能单独和他待会儿吗
Can I have a minute, please?
对不起
I'm sorry.
需要帮忙吗
You need some help?
不  我自己能行  谢谢
Hmm? oh. nah, I've got it. Thanks.
Jim  潜艇明天早上出发
Hey, Jim, the sub leaving tomorrow morning--
两周以后回来
It returns in two weeks.
到那之前
Until then,
你可以待在这里继续寻找剩下的人
You can stay and look for the rest of your crew.
谢谢
Thanks.
我为我们争取了两周的时间
I bought us two weeks.
Horace说我们可以等下一趟潜艇
Horace said we can wait for the next sub.
运气好的话  Locke到时会回来
Any luck, locke'll be back by then.
然后呢
And then what?
你问"然后呢"是什么意思
What do you mean, "then what"?
Locke说他马上就来救我们
Locke said he was leaving to save us.
闪光停止了
The flashes have stopped.
结束了
They're over.
不会再流鼻血了
No more bloody noses.
我们已经获救了
We're already saved.
你后面那趟潜艇把我带到这里来
That sub behind you brought me here.
三年来我都试图离开这个岛
I've been trying to get off of this island
现在我有机会了
For more than three years, and now I've got my chance.
我要离开
I'm going to leave.
你应该知道现在是1974年
You do realize it's 1974,
不管你想回到哪里...
That whatever it is you think you're going back to...
那儿都还不存在
It don't exist yet.
这不是留下来的理由
It's not a reason not to go.
好吧  那我怎么办
Well, what about me?
你真的想留下我和这个疯科学家
You really gonna leave me here with the mad scientist
和"我和死人说话"先生在一起
And Mr. "I speak to dead people"?
还有那个  这家伙真是个好人
And Jin, who's a hell of a nice guy
但实在不是健谈的人
But not exactly the greatest conversationalist.
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
也许
Maybe...
但是谁来带我回去呢
But who's gonna get my back?
别这样
Come on.
我全部要求就是  给我两周时间
Just give me two weeks, that's all I'm asking.
两周
Two weeks.
好吧  就两周
All right. two weeks.
三年后
Three years later
什么东西闻起来好香
Mmm, somethin' smells good.
你回来了
Hey there.
是给我的吗
Is that for me?
你今天真漂亮
You were amazing today.
谢谢你相信我
Thank you for believing in me.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
醒醒  老大
Wake up, boss.
你的头怎么样
How's your head?
好疼
It hurts.
我有好消息也有坏消息
I got good news and bad news.
你先听哪个
What you want first?
好消息
Good news.
你做爸爸了
You're a daddy.
坏消息是你错过了
Bad news is you missed it.
天啊
Oh, gosh.
Amy  她生孩子了
Amy... she had the baby?
是个男孩
It's a boy.
男孩
A boy?
现在和我说说
Now how about you tell me
为什么你喝得酩酊大醉还大发脾气
Why you're too busy drinkin' and blowin' up trees
而没有看着他出生
To see him be born?
我在
I was, uh...
我在找双袜子
I was looking for a pair of socks,
我的都脏了
And all of mine were dirty,
所以我去拿一双Amy的  然后
So I went to grab a pair of amy's, and...
我就发现了这个
I found this...
在她抽屉的后面
In the back of her drawer.
这是Paul的
It was Paul's.
你就为了一条项链去打架
You got in a fight over a necklace?
我知道
I know.
但是
But...
只有三年而以  Jim
It's only been three years, Jim.
他只离开了三年而以
Just three years that he's been gone.
这点时间真的足够忘掉一个人吗
Is that really long enough to get over someone?
我曾经有过一个女孩
I had a thing for a girl once.
而且我试过追求她
And I had a shot at her,
但是我没成功
But I didn't take it.
一段时间里  我每晚躺在床上
For a little while, I'd lay in bed every night,
都怀疑这是一场错误
Wondering if it was a mistake.
怀疑
Wondering if...
我是否可以不再想她
I'd ever stop thinking about her.
而现在我几乎记不得她的样子
And now I can barely remember what she looks like.
她的脸...
I mean, her face--it's...
她离开了
She's just gone,
就再也没回来
And she ain't never coming back.
那么
So...
三年的时间足够忘掉一个人吗
Is three years long enough to get over someone?
绝对够了
Absolutely.
怎么啦
What?
等等  怎么啦
Wait. what?
不  不
H--no. no.
别让他们进来
Don't bring 'em in.
我们在北部峡谷见面
Just meet me in the north valley.
是谁啊
Who was it?
James  怎么了
James, what's going on?
是Jin
It was Jin.
没事吧
Is everything okay?
没事  我只是  我得去
Yeah. I just... I gotta go.